Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Milne Library Preservation Project Photographs, ca. 2003
  - "In the Year 1910, JUNE 30th Glenn Curtiss Flew From Van Rensselaer Island, Albany, N.Y. To Governor's Island, New York" Milne 200 Mural, 1943 October
  - "1943 Capitol Hill Modern Albany 1943 Three Forms of Architecture" Milne 200 Mural, 1943 October
  - Milne 200, Frieze 1, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 2, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 3, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 4, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 5 A, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 5 B, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 5 C, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 6, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 7, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 8, 1929 February
  - Milne 200, Frieze 9, 1929 February
  - Recording of dedication of the Milne Commons Room, 1984 September 1
  - Donor List for Milne School Alumni Digital Reformatting Project, 2012